import { Question } from "../App";

export const himymData: Question[] =
    [
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the bar where the group frequently hangs out?",
            "options": ["MacLaren's Pub", "Puzzles", "Central Perk", "The Drunken Clam"],
            "answer": "MacLaren's Pub"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is known for saying, 'Suit up!'?",
            "options": ["Barney Stinson", "Ted Mosby", "Marshall Eriksen", "Robin Scherbatsky"],
            "answer": "Barney Stinson"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Ted's architecture firm?",
            "options": ["Mosbius Designs", "GNB Architects", "Stinson Enterprises", "Mosby & Co."],
            "answer": "Mosbius Designs"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who does Barney marry?",
            "options": ["Robin Scherbatsky", "Nora", "Quinn", "Patrice"],
            "answer": "Robin Scherbatsky"
        },
        {
            "question": "What instrument does Ted's future wife play?",
            "options": ["Bass Guitar", "Violin", "Piano", "Trumpet"],
            "answer": "Bass Guitar"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the playbook Barney uses?",
            "options": ["The Playbook", "The Bro Code", "The Legendary Book", "Suit Up Guide"],
            "answer": "The Playbook"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Robin's pop star alter ego's stage name?",
            "options": ["Robin Sparkles", "Robin Daggers", "Jessica Glitter", "Tiffany"],
            "answer": "Robin Sparkles"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which character is obsessed with finding the best burger in New York?",
            "options": ["Marshall Eriksen", "Ted Mosby", "Barney Stinson", "Lily Aldrin"],
            "answer": "Marshall Eriksen"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did Ted meet the Mother?",
            "options": ["At the Farhampton train station", "MacLaren's Pub", "In a class", "At a wedding"],
            "answer": "At the Farhampton train station"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the nickname given to Barney's brother James?",
            "options": ["J-Dawg", "Jimmy the Stinson", "Swarlos", "Big Daddy James"],
            "answer": "Swarlos"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Lily and Marshallâ€™s first child?",
            "options": ["Marvin", "Daisy", "Penny", "Luke"],
            "answer": "Marvin"
        }
    ];
